If you have purchased the ICC card on Amazon after
watching the video of Profit News, then
you must review this review to know
what benefits you actually get in it
or not. First of all, we had
told him in the video that
we will get a benefit of Rs 3000 plus, which I would
like to correct, we will get a
benefit of Rs 2000 plus and what is happening is Rs 1000 less,
in the beginning itself I had said
that we will get a
voucher of Rs 1800 plus a voucher of Rs 200 plus
whatever different features we have, like if you make
electricity bill payment,
you were getting benefits of Rs
250, Rs 100, whenever after adding that, we used to get up
to Rs 3000, but it is not so, that benefit
is inclusive and along with that we are getting, along with that
we have got up to Rs 650,
we are getting Prime membership of Easy Diner,
so this benefit is of Prime member.  You will
get 2000 for this and 1800 for non-prime.
Now the card which I had played has been sent to me
and as soon as I have the card
here, all my vouchers are credited in my Amazon account
here. So let me
show you all the vouchers. First of all,
see, I got 250
on electricity bill and 20% so that I will have to do a
transaction of around 1250 to
get the full benefit of it.
Then similarly, I got a bag worth ₹100. I got
mobile and prepaid and postpaid worth
300. Then again, suppose my friends, there are two
of 300 each, after that there is one DTH of 250
and after that there are two gas cylinders,
two of 125 each and there is a 350 pack of broadband bill.
So friends, I am getting all this together. If
you see the calculation, then it is around
1800 and 200 was
credited to my account on the first transaction. So
I  Let me show you, I
redeemed some of these vouchers from this, as you can see,
I have redeemed this for DTH
recharge and I have redeemed the
electricity bill here, so did I get anything, let me
show you what I
got and what not, so that we can
see from this side, friends, I have received it, I have paid the
electricity bill, I have
recharged the details, I have got 250
and in this way I have got 700, so till now
700 has been deposited with me on Amazon,
I can redeem this for anything at any time for the next one year,
apart from this, the rest of the vouchers which I have read right now, which
I have not redeemed, I will redeem them
and I will avail the benefit of that too here,
apart from this, whenever I did a
transaction, I got 2%
cashback in it, that means if I
paid electricity bill of 1250, then I
got cashback of 25 rupees here, so this is
over and about this and I have redeemed 1000  I have done
DTH, so I got ₹20 in that,
which means 2% cashback. I do any transaction,
I have got 2% cashback, total I have got 745
till now, so it is not 3000, it
is 2000 benefit but it is a benefit and
anyway I did not have to pay anything, the
card came directly to my home, I did not have to do
anything, so what can be a better benefit than this,
I thought friends,
I will give you a review so that when you also take
advantage of it, you should keep this in mind.
Thank you, so match friends, bye bye